Joan Mayer Campbell

10523 Washington Street, Chagrin Falls, Ohio 44023 https://www.linkedin.com/in/joanmayercampbell

joanmayercampbell@gmail.com 440-241-7920

Professional Profile

I am a Software Developer with training in the Visual Studio development environment and ASP.net MVC framework. My coding skills include C#, SQL, HTML/CSS, Java, JavaScript, JQuery. I have experience with Object Oriented Programming and scrum in the Agile framework for completing projects. My recent training has built on a foundation of education and work experience in the software development field to give me a working knowledge of the latest development environment and methodologies.

Education

- Certificate of Software Development, We Can {Code} IT
 C#, SQL, Java, JavaScript, CSS, JQuery, ASP.net MVC, Agile, Visual Studio, OOP
- BS Computer Science, University of Houston
- Medical Assistant, Capital Technical Institute, Austin, Texas
- High school Diploma, Kodaikanal International School, India

Experience

Auburn Landscape Inc., Chagrin Falls, OH Office Manager/Software Developer 5/1991 - present

- Manage employees, customer relations and marketing
- Using QuickBooks, complete payroll, quarterly taxes, Account Payable
- Developed dBase applications to handle Accounts Receivable, additional payroll enhancements and cost analysis

IBM – POS Division, Cleveland, OH

Systems Engineer

4/1986 - 5/1991

- Member of a team successful in marketing IBM POS system to major drug store chain
- Developed requirements for customizing POS to customer specifications
- Implement all coding changes
- Managed Help Desk during software installation, training personnel and identifying software issues

IBM – NASA Division, Clear Lake City, TX

Systems Engineer

1/1983 - 4/1986

- Member of a team successful in winning a bid to write software to link multiple vendor's workstations to a proprietary NASA Local Area Network (LAN)
- Designed and developed software written in C on a HP UNIX workstation to receive telemetry data from the Space Shuttle on the LAN

Volunteer:

Case Western's think[box] (maker space)